{
    "subject": "resource/Cottage_to_Let",
    "predicate": "ontology/starring",
    "object": "resource/George_Cole_(actor)",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Cottage to Let' stars George Cole.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9628627896308899,
            "question": "What role does George Cole play in 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8723384737968445,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7740717530250549,
            "question": "Are there any other famous actors in 'Cottage to Let' besides George Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7479327917098999,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring George Cole?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7408968210220337,
            "question": "Who directed 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6449042558670044,
            "question": "Where was 'Cottage to Let' filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6211574077606201,
            "question": "What is the plot of 'Cottage to Let'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5563443303108215,
            "question": "When was the film 'Cottage to Let' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4390242397785187,
            "question": "Is 'Cottage to Let' a comedy, drama, or another genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34489718079566956,
            "question": "What are some critical reviews of 'Cottage to Let'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Cottage to Let' stars George Cole.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3803_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'Cottage to Let' a comedy, drama, or another genre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3803_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'Cottage to Let' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3803_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the plot of 'Cottage to Let'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3803_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3803_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that George Cole was a young evacuee in the wartime thriller 'Cottage to Let', alongside long-time friend, Alastair Sim. This supports the claim that the film 'Cottage to Let' stars George Cole."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents mention that George Cole played a role in the film \"Cottage to Let,\" which supports the statement that the film stars George Cole."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}